wonderscope.com 2019-04-18

# Within: Privacy Policy

Effective Date: October 5, 2018 

Welcome to Within Unlimited, Inc. (“ **Company** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ” and/or “ **our** ”). We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect and disclose information and data when you use the Company website ("Site") and Company services, including any software, mobile applications, products, devices or other services offered by Company from time to time and other services offered through third parties integrating Company functionality (collectively, “ **Services** ”). “ **You** ”refers to you as a user of the Site or Services. 

###  BY USING THE SITE OR SERVICES YOU CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU ARE ARE A PARENT OR GUARDIAN OF A CHILD UNDER 13 YEARS OLD, PLEASE REVIEW OUR CHILDREN’S PRIVACY SECTION BELOW, WHICH INCLUDES DETAILS REGARDING OUR COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION IN OUR SERVICES PRIMARILY TARGETED AT CHILDREN. 

####  Managing Your Information Preferences 

You can opt out of receiving certain emails by changing notification settings on the Site or in our applications, clicking the unsubscribe link provided in an email, or by emailing us at [support@with.in](mailto:support@with.in). If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@with.in](mailto:support@with.in). 

####  Information We Collect 

#####  Personal Information 

We may collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, user name, email address, location and other personally identifiable information when you sign up for the Site or Services ("Personal Information"). The decision to provide this information is optional. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Site or Services. Except in connection with your order to purchase Services, we do not collect any credit card or other financial account information. We also collect Personal Information from you when you access the Services and/or other parts of the Site and elect to provide Personal Information. For example, when you use the Services, we will collect data that you upload to the Site and/or information that you input into your account. 

Our mobile application may collect certain additional information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device's unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the application. We may also use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location. If you do not want us to have your location information, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application. 

We allow you to use your Facebook account, Google ID or Steam Account to set up an account on our Services. If you wish to use your Facebook, Google or Steam account, you are taken to the applicable website to login to your account and the information identified by Facebook, Google or Steam, as applicable, is then shared with us for the purpose of setting up your account with us. 

#####  Usage Data and Site Activity 

We automatically collect information regarding the actions you take on the Site and Services (“ **Usage Data** ”). Usage Data is information or content we collect about the use of our Site or Services in a way that does not identify an individual user. Usage Data helps us understand trends in our users' needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor or enhance our Services. This Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of Usage Data, and we may share Usage Data about our users with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customers' needs and improve our Services. For example, each time you use the Site we may automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, how you interact with links on the Services, comments and other content you post via the Services and the time and duration of your visits to the Site. This Usage Data may be associated with your account, but we do not disclose your Personal Information to third parties unless otherwise provided herein. We may store such Usage Data itself and/or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Company affiliates, agents or service providers. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, etc. 

#####  Cookies and Web Beacons 

We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We may also use Web beacons (a file placed on a website that monitors usage). We may use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Site and Services, such as pre-populating your user name for easier login, and to collect information about traffic to our Services and how users use our Services. We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. At this time, Company does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking, including “do-not-track” signals. You can remove persistent cookies and change your privacy preferences by following directions provided in your Internet browser's “help” directory. However, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, as further explained below. 

#####  Analytics 

We use Google Analytics Advertising Features, including: Remarketing with Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting. For information about Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs, please [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) . You can also opt out of the above Google Analytics Advertising Features or adjust your settings via Google's “Ads Settings” feature and you can generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or who follow the [Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising ](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI site and DAA site. 

####  How We Use Information and When We May Share and Disclose Information Generally 

We may use your Personal Information for the purpose for which it was provided, including without limitation for the purposes described further below: 

  * Provision and Monitoring of the Services: We will use your Personal Information to provide you with access to and to support your use of the Services and to monitor your use of the Services. We may also give you the opportunity to store, review and edit Personal Information and other information on the Site. 
  * Surveys, Contests and Other Special Offers: From time to time, we may offer our users the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests and other special offers. If you elect to participate in these services, you will need to provide certain Personal Information. 
  * Questions and Requests: If you contact us by e-mail or otherwise, we will use the Personal Information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. 
  * Contacting You About Other Products, Services and Events: If you opt-in, Company and/or third parties may use your Personal Information to contact you in the future to tell you about products, services and events that may be of interest to you. 
  * Research and Data Analysis: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Site and the Services, Company may conduct research on its customers' demographics, interests and behavior based on Usage Data and other information provided to us. This data may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Company may share this data with advertisers, researchers, business partners, publications, and other third parties. This information will not identify you personally. 
  * Service Improvement: We may use your Personal Information, aggregated Personal Information and other non-personally-identifiable information collected through the Site and Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. 
  * Order Fulfillment: We may use your Personal Information that you provide to fulfill any orders you may place for Services offered by Company. 
  * No Automated Decision Making: We do not use your Personal Information for the purposes of automated decision-making. However, we may do so in order to fulfil obligations imposed by law, in which case we will inform you of any such processing and provide you with an opportunity to object. 

####  Information You Make Available to Others 

By using the Site or Services, including creation of a profile or submission of public queries, you may make certain of your Personal Information available to others, such as your name, your user name, and your picture. This information may be accessed by users who use the Site or Services and may be accessed by commercial search engines such as Google, Yahoo!, and Bing to the extent that such engines are permitted to access the Site or Services. 

####  Third Party Services and Applications 

Through the Site or Services, you may elect to access third-party services and applications, such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and other social networks. When you do so, you may be able to import information from those other services and applications and share content with those services. Some of those third-party services may also provide us with information from your accounts, which may enable us to enhance and personalize your use of the Site and Services. If you elect to enable such third-party services or applications, the information you share with such third-party services and applications will be subject to their privacy policies and your privacy settings. You may also be able to control whether your activity is sent to third-party services and applications by changing the relevant settings in your Company account (if any). You also may be able to control or block such sharing by changing your privacy settings in such services or applications. Third parties may collect, but we do not authorize them to collect, personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Site or Services. 

####  Service Providers 

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses that we believe to be trustworthy and have privacy practices consistent with ours (“ **Service Providers** ”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by Company. 

####  Advertising 

We may work with third-party advertisers, search providers, and ad networks (“ **Advertisers** ”). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Site or Services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the Site, the Services, or third-party websites and online services. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that Advertisers may collect from you or that you choose to provide to them. 

####  Other Transfers 

We may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Company. If Company is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets or equity, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction. 

####  Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement 

Company will cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other content and information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of Company or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. 

####  Be Careful When You Share Information with Others 

Please be aware that whenever you share information on a publicly available page or any other public forum on the Site or Services, others may access that information. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications. 

####  Exclusions 

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Company through the Site or Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as bulletin boards, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Company shall be free, and you hereby grant Company the right, to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution. 

####  Security 

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information and other information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, and you do so at your own risk. 

####  Links 

Our Site and Services may contain links or integrate with other websites and online services, or allow others to send you such links. Company is not responsible or liable for any damage or loss related to your use of any third-party website or online service. You should always read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of a third-party website or online service before using it, whether directly or in connection with your use of the Site or Services. 

####  Children's Privacy 

We offer to our users a range of Services, some of which are primarily targeted at children, and others that are intended for users of all ages and their families. We are required under the Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), with limited exceptions, to obtain verifiable parental consent in order to collect, use, or disclose Personal Information from children. 

Many of our Services are intended for general audiences and do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children. If our Services request age information from your child and your child indicates that he/she is under 13 years old, the Service will block your child from providing personal information. **Please note, that if your child indicates that he/she is under the age of 13, your child WILL NOT be blocked from using our Services.**

For our Services that are primarily directed at children under the age of 13, we do not collect Personal Information, except in those instances under COPPA where Personal Information may be collected without verifiable parental consent. For example, if your child provides us feedback or contacts us (for support, for example), we will collect the data included in the communication. We will use this personal information to assist your child with his/her query or support request and then delete such information once we have fulfilled the child’s query or support request. We do not share your child’s personal information with third parties, other than as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If you believe that we might have any Personal Data from a child under 13, please contact us at [support@with.in](mailto:support@with.in). 

####  Processing in the United States 

Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. By using our Site or Services, you agree that the applicable laws in the United States will govern the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By providing your data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

####  Your Rights 

Opt-out. You may contact us any time to opt-out of: (a) direct marketing communications; (b) automated decision-making and/or profiling; (c) our collection of sensitive personal data; (d) any new processing of your Personal Information that we may carry out beyond the original purpose; or (e) the transfer of your Personal Information to places other than the United States. Please note that your use of some of the Services may be ineffective upon opt-out. 

Access. You may access the data we hold about you at any time by contacting us directly. 

Amend. You can also contact us to update or correct any inaccuracies in your Personal Information. 

Move. Your data is portable, so you have the flexibility to move your Personal Information and data to other service providers as you wish. 

Ease and forget. In certain situations, for example, when the Personal Information and data we hold about you is no longer relevant or is incorrect, you can request that we erase your data. 

Retention. We will only retain your Personal Information as required for you to use the Services and/or to provide you with the Services, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (for example, for regulatory purposes). 

You may contact us at [support@with.in](mailto:support@with.in) or Within Unlimited, Inc., Privacy Policy Inquiry, 3760 Motor Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90034 any time for any other questions you may have about your Personal Information, our use of such Personal Information, or to exercise one of your rights described above. 

####  Privacy Policy Changes 

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will give you notice by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and within our Services. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Site or Services, you consent to the revised Privacy Policy. 

PLEASE PRINT A COPY OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR YOUR RECORDS AND PLEASE CHECK THE SITE FREQUENTLY FOR ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
